Let's go, baby. Clean the building.
Good
>> to meet you.
>> Oh, not bad.
>> Perfect. I'm going to have your
breakfast here just shortly as you
finish up this first part and then we'll
get all
>> sounds good.
I'm excited, man. I'm excited. Happy to
be here. Prayed for it and it worked
out, man. So thankful to be here, baby.
>> Mario, welcome back, man.
>> It's good to be back, man. Thank you.
>> Hey. Hey.
>> How you doing, Damario?
>> Hey, my bad. I got chocolate.
I got good [__] in. Hey,
>> fine, bro. What's up?
>> What's up,
>> Hey, you look good though, boy. You look
good, man. Step it up for you.
>> What's up, man? Welcome, man. Thank you.
Well,
>> appreciate that. Yes, sir. But glad to
get you here.
>> Yes, sir.
>> You enjoy it. Any questions, let us all
know. Anything you, you know, pops the
head. Restaurants,
>> all that kind of stuff, you name it, we
have it here. So, okay.
>> Enjoy the visit.
>> Big food people. So,
>> excited to love it.
Yeah. It's crazy how fast they can go.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm going to wear it.
>> Oh, you look good. [laughter]
You look so good.
>> He's like, "Do I?" Yeah. Okay.
>> Oh my goodness.
>> Uh, today's day is the 12th.
>> Yes.
Perfect. Congrats. It's officially
official. Welcome back. Thank you,
>> man. I'm definitely excited um just to
be here um a part of this organization
and um just ready to get here and uh
turn things around and uh contribute.
>> It's a very uh surreal experience
um to be in this game for going on 15
seasons. Um, and I kind of walk down the
hallways and uh, what feels like a
lifetime ago, all the faces on the wall
are now like historic people. Derel
Rivas, Dave Harris, Bart Scott, uh, Nick
Mango, rest in peace, the Brick Al
Ferguson. Seeing their face plastered
throughout the building, I was just a
young man. Um, it's a very surreal
experience and uh, really excited.
>> How you doing, man? Hey, good to see
you, man.
>> Nice to see you, too. Welcome back.
>> Oh, man. Looking good still, man. I know
you met my wife.
>> How are you?
>> Pleasure to meet you. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you. Welcome back.
>> Hey, it's good to be back.
>> It's awesome. This is incredible.
>> Incredible.
>> Hello.
>> Oh, media.
>> Yep.
>> We're fine. We promise.
>> Yeah,
>> I hope so.
He's big. Cool.
Cool. And I'll have you like flip
through the pages as if you're like
checking everything and looking through.
>> Perfect. Okay, I'll have you look here.
Three, two, Oh my goodness. [laughter]
>> That's perfect.
>> Absolute star.
>> Holy cow.
>> What's up, Jess Nation? This is Joseph
Assai reporting for duty official.
unofficially.
>> Officially he's camp officially. I'm
signed.
>> Thank you guys for having me. Um I'm so
excited to be here. I can't wait to get
to work and make you guys proud. Let's
go.
>> If you're good with it, I am. But you
could also redo it.
>> You don't like it? [laughter]
>> HOW ABOUT WE DO one for safety when you
make a choice?
>> Well, now you know
>> who's picking though. Who's picking the
video?
>> That would be me.
>> So, you didn't like it?
>> No. [laughter] I just think like there
are parts that if you wanted to be
better, you could.
>> Okay.
>> Constructive digital.
>> Reminder, you're officially
>> officially
nation. It's Joseph Oai
>> reporting for duty.
>> It's official.
>> Officially signed.
>> Get the word.
>> I love you guys. Too soon. [laughter]
>> No, I do like that. That's good.
>> Too soon. [laughter]
>> All right. One more time. Third time's a
charm.
>> You got it.
>> Yeah.
>> What's up, Jess Nation? This is Joseph
Asai reporting for duty. Um, I'm so
excited to be here. We just put pen in
the paper and I can't wait to get to
work. Let's go. J E Ts. Jets. Jets.
Jets. Yes, sir.
>> Perfect.
>> Good job.
>> Yeah, that was good. That was really
good.
>> So, if you just sign there and then
we'll upload it.
>> Better driver is New York or Miami.
>> Oh, I was just talking about this with
my mom. So we we said that Miami drivers
are more like crazy like they do just
crazy stuff on the road. New York
drivers are just meaner.
>> They ran their seat right
for the dot.
>> Yeah. This is roughly 26.
>> You were all good.
>> All right. Kingsley, how would how would
you describe your excitement coming in
the building today and beginning this
new chapter of your career with the
Jets?
>> Um it's exciting. Like you said, there's
a new chapter and every new chapter
brings uh new excitement, new joys, new
memories.
>> Thanks, guys. These are all
the right way.
>> But if you want to walk in the city,
there's a train station.
>> I'll just have you stay on for a little
bit longer.
So, we'll we'll go up size and then
we'll make adjustments. Sounds good. All
right. Sounds good. All right. Thank you
so much.
>> I have not.
>> Yeah.
>> A
>> big J.
>> Beautiful.
>> Yes sir.
>> Your pads will be up here. All you got
to do is hit this button right here.
Oh wow.
>> Got you.
We have to pull that jersey out.
>> Guys, welcome. Welcome to the Jets
family. Good to have your jersey back,
man.
>> Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
>> M. What's your impression of Aaron Glenn
and the defense that, you know, the Jets
have built now this all season?
>> Yeah. Um, I'm I'm really excited to to
to play for for for coach. Um, you know,
I think he views the game in a very
similar uh manner to a lot a lot of guys
that that play my position. So, we have
all the necessary parts to to be a
really really great defense under uh the
guidance of AG and Dooker and and those
guys. So, once my agents let me know
that the Jets were option, it was a
no-brainer. And I've been watching AG
from from afar. I didn't even need to
have a conversation with him to to be
all on board and to get here and see
what it is that he's building and the
culture and just to feel the the energy
in the building. Just a ton of
excitement.
>> Thank you Mario.
>> All right. Thank you guys. Y'all be
blessed.